{
    "subject": "resource/Ran_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_films",
    "human_readable": "Ran (film) is about American films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8089080452919006,
            "question": "Is 'Ran' a Japanese or American film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7630983591079712,
            "question": "How does 'Ran' compare to other films about American cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.754317045211792,
            "question": "What is the subject of the film 'Ran'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6790916919708252,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Ran'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5108705759048462,
            "question": "What genre of films does 'Ran' explore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45966798067092896,
            "question": "What are some common elements found in films about American cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3936397433280945,
            "question": "What are some critical responses to the film 'Ran'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18670421838760376,
            "question": "Does 'Ran' feature any iconic scenes or imagery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18351101875305176,
            "question": "What is the primary theme explored in 'Ran'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16897906363010406,
            "question": "What historical period or setting does 'Ran' likely portray?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ran (film) is about American films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6860_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary theme explored in 'Ran'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6860_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does 'Ran' feature any iconic scenes or imagery?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6860_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some critical responses to the film 'Ran'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6860_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6860_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6860_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6860_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6860_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6860_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6860_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6860_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6860_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6860_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6860_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThis is because none of the documents mention that Ran (film) is about American films. The documents actually suggest that Ran is a Japanese film, inspired by Shakespeare's King Lear and Japanese legend and culture."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided in the documents discusses the film \"Ran\" directed by Akira Kurosawa and its themes, inspiration, and production details. There is no mention of \"American films\" or any American author/director in relation to \"Ran.\" Therefore, the statement that \"Ran (film) is about American films\" is incorrect based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}